A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty
circa 1896-1980
Rockefeller Archive Center
Cohn, Alfred E. (Alfred Einstein)
FA132
20 Cubic Feet 43 document boxes and 1 oversize box.
43 document boxes and one oversize box.
Biographical/Historical note
Alfred Einstein Cohn, 16 April 1879-20 July 1957.
Physician, humanist, and author. One of first physicians in the United States to make electrocardiograms (Mount Sinai Hospital, New York City, 1910). Clinical researcher at The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, New York City, 1911-1957.
Scope and Contents note
Biographical material, professional and personal correspondence, family letters, board and committee records, manuscripts of scientific and popular writings, notes, photographs, printed materials. Primarily correspondence and writings about heart disease including on aging, arteriosclerosis, digitalis, electrocardiography, hypertension, statistics, World War I cardiac neuroses. Also extensive material on social issues including émigré and refugee physicians and scholars from Europe; medicine in China; Blacks in medicine; graduate and medical education; post-World War II organization of science; psychiatry and psychoanalysis; Alger Hiss case. Correspondents include: Charles A. Beard (1874-1948), Samuel Nathaniel Behrman (1893-1973), Bernard Berenson (1865-1959), Carl Binger (1889-1968), Niels Bohr (1885-1962), Maurice Bowra (1898-1971), Louis D. Brandeis (1856-1941), Alexis Carrel (1873-1944), Harvey Cushing (1869-1939), Arthur W.M. Ellis (1883-1966), John Erskine (1979-1951), Abraham Flexner (1866-1959), Bernard Flexner (1865-1945), Simon Flexner (1863-1946), Felix Frankfurter (1882-1965), Francis Fraser (1885-1964), Herbert Spencer Gasser (1888-1963), Alan Gregg (1890-1957), William Ivins (1881-1961), Henry James (1879-1947), Smith Ely Jelliffe (1866-1945), Lawrence S. Kubie (1896-1973), Karl Landsteiner (1868-1943), Harold Laski (1893-1950), Thomas Lewis (1881-1945), Franklin C. McLean (1888-1968), James Mackenzie (1853-1925), Archibald MacLeish (1892-1982), Henry Alexander Murray, Jr. (1893-), Edward R. Murrow (1908-1975), George Canby Robinson (1878-1960), Charles Singer (1876-1960), Jean Stafford (1915-1979), Mark Van Doren (1894-1972), Hermann Weyl (1885-1955), Paul Dudley White (1886-1973), Alfred N. Whitehead (1861-1947).
Organizational records include: American Society for Clinical Investigation, 1922-1956; Asia Institute, 1940-1952; China Medical Board, 1927-1953; Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars, 1933-1944; Institute for Psychoanalysis, 1932-1944; Joint Distribution Committee, 1921-1945; Journal of Clinical Investigation, 1923-1938; New School for Social Research, 1940-1952; Office of Foreign Relief, 1942-1944; Student Service of America, 1941-1948; Sydenham Hospital, 1947-1948; Veterans Bureau, 1924-1947; World's Fair, New York City, 1939.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Alfred E. Cohn.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 450 C661
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Other Finding Aids
FA802 Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty
Arrangement
The Alfred E. Cohn papers consist of four series:
1. General Correspondence,
2. Biographical material,
3. Photographs and prints,
4. Notes
Physiology; Diseases; Public health; Embryology; Pathology; Biology -- Research; Anatomy; Biochemistry; Medical care; Pharmacology; Medical research; Medical sciences; Cardiology; Medicine, Preventive; Rockefeller University; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
- General Correspondence, 1
  - Abernethy, Theodore, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abramson, Julius (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Addis, T., 1933-1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adler, Cyrus, 1928 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alden, F.A. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albright, Fuller, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Benjamin [re], 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Franz (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, John J. [re], 1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Samuel, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alice, Mother (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alpert, Louis, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alsberg, Carl L., 1932 1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Altschul, Frank, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alvarez, Walter C., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alving, Alf, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Institute of the City of New York (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Amoss (?), [Harold L.], 1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Museum of Health, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Public Health Association, 1932, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Ruth Dodd, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Andrus, E.C., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - D. Appleton-Century Co., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aschoff, L., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ascoli, Max, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Andrewes, Sir Frederick, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Andrus, E.C., 1930 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anitschkow, Prof. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aschheim, S., 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aschoff, L. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aschoff, Ludwig, 1929-1933 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ascoli, Max and Anna Maria, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aswell, Mr., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Austin, J.H., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Automobile Association, London (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aydelotte, Frank, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ayres, Louis, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anthony, Albert, 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anthony, Albert, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anthony, Albert, undated ms. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arnett, Trevor, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Austin, J. Harold, 1936 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Avery, Mr. and Mrs., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Society for Clinical Investigation, 1922-1925 1927 undated ms (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ASCI, 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ASCI, 1939-1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - [ASCI, Journal of Clinical Investigation, J. Canby Robinson], 1923-1927 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - [ASCI, JCI, J. Harold Austin], 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Society for Clinical Investigation, Journal of Clinical Investigation, J. Harold Austin, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Society for Clinical Investigation, Journal of Clinical Investigation, J. Harold Austin, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Society for Clinical Investigation, Journal of Clinical Investigation, J. Harold Austin, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ASCI, re editor-in-chief of JCI, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Applications, Department (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - American Association on Indian Affairs, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Physicians, 1928-1935 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Abstracts, Association of American Physicians (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Association of American Physicians, 1928-1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - American Medical Association, 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Associated Hospital Service, 1938-1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Abercrombie and Fitch Co., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Acheson, Dean, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ackerman, N.W., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Adamic, Louis, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Adams, Roger, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Adams, Walter, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Addis, Thomas, 1940 1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alexander, Eben, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Allen, F.L., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Altman, B. and Co., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Allender, S.S., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Altschul, F., 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Eagle Club, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Heart Journal and American Heart Association, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Medical Association, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Amberson, J.B., 1941 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Academy of Medicine, New York, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Addis, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Addis, Thomas, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Adler, Frank L., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alden, Robert, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alexander, Franz, 1946 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ahrens, Edward H., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Allen, Mr., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Allen, Lilian, 1947-1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Altschul, Frank, 1947 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American College of Surgeons, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Institute of the City of New York, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Public Health Association, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Anderson, Harold, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Andrus, E.C., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anthony, Mrs., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Antioch Review, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Archibald, R.M., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ascoli, Max, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ascoli, Marion R., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Appel, Doris, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Asgis, A.J., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Astor, Vincent, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Aswell, M.L., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Avery, Oswald T., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Andrus, W. De W., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anshen, Ruth N., 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Appel, John W., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Appleby, Paul H., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Arlein, M.S., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Aschheim, S., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ascoli, Max, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Asham, Richard, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Astrachan, Irving, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Austin, J. Harold, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Avery, Robert H., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ayers, H.E., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Brincliff?, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Barker, L.F., 1924 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bass, E., 1924 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Baehr, George, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Baehr, George (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Newton D. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bangs, C.R., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bates, J., 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bazett, H.C., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bache, D.S., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bach, F., 1929-1932 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bachrach, A.C., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barker, M., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Baehr, F., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bailey, P., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bailey, F., 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bainton, J.H., 1928 1932 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barach, A.L., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barker, L.F., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barker, P.S., 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barlow, Sir Thomas, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barnard, Eunice F., 1928-1932 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barr, D.P. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bauer, Nettie E., 1928 1932 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bayliss, L.E., 1929 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Beardsley, John, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Beekman, Fenwick, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Benjamin, Bernard, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Benjamin, Helen R., 1934 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Benjamin, Julian E., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berensen (sic), Bernard, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berg, I., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berghoff, E., 1928 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berglund, H., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berkson, Joseph (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berle, Mr. and Mrs. Adolph, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berhard, W.G. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Berolzheimer, E. Mr. and Mrs. and children, 1929-1937 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Becker, Florence, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Beeson?, P., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Baer, Rudolph L., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Baerwald, Paul, 1945 1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Backer, George, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Backer, George (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Barnard, Chester I., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Barnes, A.R., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bauer, G.E., 1947 1949 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bayne-Jones, S., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Ball, C.R., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Banks, Mrs. Frank, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Banta, George Publishing Co., 1940 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Barach, Alvan L., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Barker, Paul S., 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Baron, Salo, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Barrett, Michael, 1941 1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Baruch, Bernard, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Baskette, E.C., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bauer, Donald, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Beard, Charles and Mary, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Beaulieu, Avid, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Behrman, S.N., 1941 1951 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Benedetti, P., 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Benjamin, J.E., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berg, A.A., 1941 1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berghoff, K., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berenson, Bernard, 1942 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bergmann, Max, 1941-1942 1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berk, L.H., 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berkingoff, David, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berkson, Seymour, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bernstein, Felix, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berol, Albert, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Berolzheimer, Edwin and Myra, 1940-1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Better Times, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bell, Book and Candle, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Belsinger, E.R., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Benda, C.E., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Berger, Elmer, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Berle, Adolph A. Mrs., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bernays, Hella, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Berol, Alfred C., 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Berolzheimer, Myra, Edwin, and Margot Craig, 1946-1948 1951 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bearn, A.G., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Beard, Charles and Mary, 1924 1931-1932 1935 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Berenson, Bernard, 1946 1949 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Binger, Carl, 1921-1952 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Binger, Carl (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bilhuber, E., 1924 1927 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Black, D., 1926 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blake, F.G., 1924 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bluestone, Dr., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Billings, H., 1935 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Binger, Walter D., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Biological Abstracts, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blake, Francis G., 1929 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blake, Gwen, 1930-1933 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blanton, W.B., 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bloom, Honorable Sol (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bluestone, E.M., 1930-1936 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blumer, G., 1930 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bliss, D.W., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - B?, George, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bixler, F., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blake, Francis G., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bliven, Bruce, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bluestone, E.M., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Billikopf, J., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Billikopf, J. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Billings, H.S. and Mrs., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bingham, Mrs., 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Biological Sciences, American Institute of, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Biondo,?, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Blackstone Photographers, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Blake, Francis G., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bios, P. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bluestone, E.M., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Blumgart, Hermann, 1925-1935 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Boggs, T.R., 1924-1926 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Boldyroff, W.N., 1924 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Boyden, E.A., 1923-1926 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bolaffio, R.E., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bowra, Maurice, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Boudreau, F.G., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Boyd, J.P., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bohr, Niels, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Boas, E.P., 1929-1939 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Boas, E.P. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Boas, Barbara, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Boas, Franz, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Beard, Charles A. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bock, A.V., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boggs, T.R., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bogue, J.Y., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Böhm, R., 1935 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bohnenkamp, H., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bolduan, C.F., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bolte, Charles G. and Mary, 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bond, Philip, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boorum, M.M. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boots, R.H., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boring, Edwin G., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Botzow, Elizabeth, 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boudrau, F.G., 1934-1935 1947 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bowra, Maurice, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bramwell, C., 1946 1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bright, Mrs., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brinton, C., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brodman, E., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bronk, D.W., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brown, D., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brown, M.C., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brownell, G.A. Mrs., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bruck, M.A., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brunner, R., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bryant, J.M., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bryson, Lyman, 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Briercliffe, R., 1924 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bramwell, C., 1929 1932 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Branch, Arnold, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Braun, W.A., 1926 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brettauer, J., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brody, Samuel, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bronfenbrenner, J., 1933-1935 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brooke, Helen C., undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brooks, Harlow, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Thomas R., 1930 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Wade H., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brown, David A., 1925 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brandeis, Louis and Mrs., 1930-1939 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Brandeis, Louis (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bramwell, J.C., 1938-1941 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brauman, Mrs., undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Braun, W.A. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brentano's, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bridgman, P.W., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - British Library of Information, 1936 1938 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brody, Samuel, 1937-1941 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bronfenbrenner, M., 1940 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bronisch, G.P., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Hospital, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Science, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brown, A., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brown, Ethel B. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brown, Ruth G. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brown, William E., 1938 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bruce, E., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bruch, Hilde, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bruck, Max A., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brunswick, Max A., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bryson, Lyman, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Böhmig, R., 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bramwell, J.C., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Büchner, Dr., 1930 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Buckley, A.V., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Buckner, E.R. and Mrs., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Buell, R.L., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Buffinton, E. Mrs., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bulloch, William, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bullowa, J.G.M., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burgan, H.C., 1930 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burlingame, C.C., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burnett, C.T., 1929 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burroughs, Betty, 1940 1946 1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burroughs, Louise, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burrow, Trigant, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burwell, C. Sidney, 1927 1934-1936 1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burwell, C.S. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Butcher, Harold, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Buttenweiser, B.J. Mrs., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Buxton, F.W., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bull, W.E., 1930 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Burlingham, C.C., 1936 1938-1944 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Burch, George, 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Burch, George, 1939-1953 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cohn, Peter (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Calhoun, W.J. Mrs., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Campbell, Virginia, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Campbell, Editha, 1936-1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cane, Linda R., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cane, Melville, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cannan, R.K. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cannon, W.B., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Carrel, Alexis, 1937 1939 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Castiglioni, Arturo, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cates, Natalie, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1936-1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cahan, Jacob M., 1932 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cameron, D.J., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cane, Florence and Melville, 1928-1932 1935 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cannan, R.K., 1935 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carabba, Victor, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carlson, A.J., 1928 1930 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cannon, W.B., 1930 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carns, Carrie R., 1932 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carter, Edward P., 1928-1930 1933 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carter, E.C., 1928 1931 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carter, Henry R. Jr., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carter, W.S., 1930-1934 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cartwright, M.A., 1929-1935 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Carty, John J., 1930 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Castiglioni, Prof (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1928-1935 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Cecil, Russell, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Campo, Anthony J., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cane, Melville, 1940-1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cann, Norman D., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cannon, Walter B., 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Calderone, Frank A., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Carlton, Winslow, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Carney, C.T., 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Carrel, Alexis (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Carrel, Alexis, 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Carter, William D., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Carse, Robert, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cartier, Inc., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cash, James, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Casper, Wolfgang, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cassidy, George, 1940-1941 1944 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Castiglioni, Arturo, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Castiglioni, A. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1940-1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cattell, Jacques (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Causey, J.H., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Caldwell, Otis, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Carlson, A.J., 1924 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Carter, E.C., 1926-1927 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Carter, E.P., 1926 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Carter, H.R. Jr., 1926 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cecil, Russell L., 1923 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cambridge Instrument Co., 1922-1932 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Campobello Institute, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Carrel, Alexis, 1923-1935 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chalet, Louis, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chambers, Robert, 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chase, Ethel, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cheifetz, Herman, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cheer, S.N., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chesney, Alan, 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chesney, A. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Children's Welfare Federation of New York City, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chitty, William D., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Christian, Henry A., 1935 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Christie, Ronald V., undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Clark, L. May, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Clark, Grover, 1928-1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cline, May, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cloetta, M., 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chace, Arthur F., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chase, Harry W., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chase, Harry W. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chesney, Alan M., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chickering, H.T., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Christian, Henry A., 1935-1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Christie, Ronald V., 1936 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clark, Grenville (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chaucer Head Book Shop, 1936-1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Campo, Anthony J., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Carson, William J. Mrs., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cattell, Jacques, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cattell, McKeen, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cane, Melville, 1947-1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cecil, Russell L., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chamberlain, J.P., 1924 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cheer, Sheonan, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Grover, 1925-1926 (Box 6, Folder 2)